Turn. turn. There's the sign.
Oh. my gosh.
I can't believe we're finally here.
Oh. wait. I told Shane I'd text him
once we're almost there.
Oh. Mitchie...
- What?
- Nothing. nothing.
Mom. obviously it's something.
I mean. you and subtle
aren't very good friends.
I know you and Shane talk all the time.
but. you know. it's...
You actually haven't seen this boy
in almost a year.
I just don't want you to be
too disappointed
if he can't come to camp this summer.
Mom.
I want you to have fun
and focus on your music.
Okay. first off.
this is gonna be the best summer ever.
And second. nothing can make me
lose my focus.
What is that?
Did somebody open another camp?
Seriously. why would somebody
open up another camp across the lake?
Oh. who knows. but I don't think
it's anything to worry about.
- Aah! Caitlyn!
- Mitchie!
Whew!
- Hi!
- Caitlyn!
- How are you?
- I'm great.
- Let me take this for you.
- Thank you.
I was so afraid that we weren't
gonna get here in time.
- but doesn't look like many are here.
- You know what this means.
Since we're the first ones here.
we totally get our choice of...
...bunk.
I bet you sounded fantastic.
Yeah? Oh. my gosh.
Well. I guess no one cares
about my life.
What don't we know? I mean. you update
your status. like. every two seconds.
Fine.
- I have a question. and it's for Mitchie.
- For me?
So. what's going on with you
and Shane?
- Huh?
- Hm?
- Nothing is going on.
- That's a total lie.
You guys are obsessed.
No. seriously. I don't know. I just...
I feel like if we never get to spend
any time together.
then nothing is ever gonna happen.
Just one more crank and I think I got it.
That's good.
Can we please just wait for the tow truck?
Oliver tried and he couldn't get it.
That's because Oliver's
not properly motivated.
He's not trying to get to Camp Rock
before Mitchie.
We should have never taken
that shortcut.
Maybe because Oliver
doesn't even know Mitchie.
Thanks.
It's gonna be really cool.
I got it all planned.
She'll walk in. and I'll be sitting there.
and I'll say.
"Hey. Mitchie."
She's gonna be so surprised.
"Hey. Mitchie"? That's your big line?
Trust me.
Everything's cool when I do it.
I'm just excited to finally
spend some time with her.
- Oh. here you go.
- Is this from the tire?
Yeah. I saw it on the ground. Thought it
was important. so I put it in my pocket.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
How could I have told you
if I didn't remember until now?
- It's fine. Just one bolt. right?
- Mm-hm.
- We good?
- Yeah.
- Please.
- No.
- Oh. please. don't. No. no. no.
- No!
No!
No. no. no!
Told you it was important.
Where is everybody?
I know. right? There's. like.
barely anybody out there.
I sure hope you've got something
we can do at opening jam.
Because if not. I've got nothing.
Kind of. maybe. sort of. I don't know. I...
- Can we hear it?
- Sing it.
Okay.
- It's not finished.
- It's okay. Come on.
- Not anything special.
- Come on.
Last year's old news
I'm breakin' out my six-string
And playin' from my heart
- That is amazing.
- I love it.
Really? Thank you.
That's all I got so far.
I have a lot of lyrics.
but the music's not really worked out yet.
Maybe we could just sing the first part
over and over again.
- That's it.
- Really?
Nobody ever agrees with me.
- Barron! Sander!
- Hey. what's up?
- Hey.
- Hi. how you doing?
- Play it again.
- For you. Mitchie? Anything.
Let's rock.
Oh
Last year's old news
I'm breakin' out my six-string
And playin' from my heart
It's not déjà vu
'Cause it's another summer
That's how this chapter starts
I'm gonna run so fast till I can't breathe
Come along and follow me
Let's make some noise
We never did before
It's a brand-new day
Don't you see me?
Changing all my ways
So completely
This time I'm gonna sing
And you're gonna hear it
This time I'm gonna show you
That I got the spirit
It's a brand-new day
And I'm feelin' good
So drama-free
I'm all about the music
I just wanna sing
Watch me live out my dreams
I'm gonna rock that stage
And give my everything
I'm gonna dance until my feet can't move
Come along. get in the groove
Let's shine so bright
More than we did before
It's a brand-new day
Don't you see me?
Changing all my ways
So completely
This time I'm gonna sing
And you're gonna hear it
This time I'm gonna show you
That I got the spirit
It's a brand-new day
And I'm feelin' good
What you gonna do?
I'm gonna laugh
Through the summer with you
Who you gonna be?
You'll just have to watch me carefully
Where you gonna go?
Anywhere my heart wants me to go
I'm gonna sing. I'm gonna dance
I'm gonna write. I'm gonna play
I'm gonna try my hand in everything
'Cause it's a brand-new day
Don't you see me?
Changing all my ways
So completely
This time I'm gonna sing
And you're gonna hear it
This time I'm gonna show you
That I got the spirit
It's a brand-new day
Changing all my ways
- I'm changing all my ways
- This time I'm gonna sing
And you're gonna hear it
- Gonna hear it
- That I got the spirit
- Got the spirit
- It's a brand-new day
It's a brand-new day
And I'm feelin' good
Feelin' good
- Yeah! Whoo!
- Yeah!
Yes. all right.
Mitchie Torres. returning rocker. Yes!
Welcome to the heart and soul
of rock 'n' roll.
Whether you're slick and happening
or dark and jamming.
Camp Rock is the place to be. yeah?
All right!
Now. I'm sure you've noticed
that there aren't quite as many of you
as in years past. but not to worry.
- Aah!
- Ooh!
Shane!
Sorry. she does that.
Rockers. my nephews.
and Camp Rock alum.
better known to the world
as Connect Three!
Hey. Whoa!
We probably shouldn't have
tied his shoes together.
He's the one who said
he could make anything look cool.
- Whoa.
- And I believe he stands corrected.
- Shane. Are you all right?
- Yeah. I'm fine.
Surprise.
All right. They are gonna be with us
for the entire summer.
- The whole summer?
- Absolutely.
The official reason being
they miss their uncle.
But I don't think that's the entire story.
Whoo!
People are staring. You might wanna
do something. like react or wave.
Hey. guys. I'm Shane.
This is Jason and Nate.
We know it's gonna be hard.
but just treat us like normal campers.
Wow. I guess it's not
gonna be that hard.
Yeah. as I was saying. um.
we're a little smaller this year.
and that is courtesy of our new friends
across the lake. Camp Star.
founded. not so coincidentally.
by my out-to-destroy-me.
still-mad-that-I kicked-him
out-of-the-group
former bandmate. Axel Turner.
Axel Turner?
The guy who owns Star Records?
He's across the lake?
Yes. and I share your disdain. Tess.
Thank you for that.
Now. it's gonna take some effort.
but I'm sure we can all
peacefully co-exist on the lake. yeah?
We're under attack!
Nice.
- It's full of marshmallows.
- This one has chocolate.
Graham crackers.
Camp Rock's invited
to an opening-night bonfire.
No. no. no. Absolutely not. No.
Bonfire. bonfire. bonfire!
- This is a setup. For what I'm not sure.
- Come on. Brown. It'll be fun.
You said yourself
we all need to get along. right?
And it's not just because I haven't
made dessert yet.
This is really good chocolate. Isn't it?
One word: wow.
- This isn't a camp. it's a resort.
- You say that like it's a bad thing.
All right. I got it. Oh. I don't got it.
I think we should add this
to the uncool list.
A little help... A little help. please.
Thank you.
See. these are the type of things
that you can't learn over e-mail.
Maybe we should go back to that.
Guys. I'm not kidding.
Line up and wait for me.
Junior rockers. I'm serious.
Please wait.
Hey. what's up. guys?
I remember when I used to be
a junior rocker.
- Is that a camera. bud?
- Don't touch it.
What. you think I'm gonna drop it
in the water?
And if you thought that.
I guess you'd be right.
- You dropped it. Curly. You swim for it.
- Yeah.
Brown. my man. Long time.
- Hi. I'm Connie.
- Hi.
Listen. Axel.
I don't actually know what your plan is...
Whoa. whoa. whoa.
A breath and a step.
I'm beginning to remember
why I left the band.
Left the band. You left the band?
That is so rich.
Is that what you're telling people?
You. my friend. have got to stop
living in the past.
I'm trying to reach out to you here.
Reach out? Reach out by driving me
out of business. I love it.
There's no reason why we both
can't be successful.
- We both have our niche.
- Niche?
Camp Star is dedicated
to producing the superstars of tomorrow.
And what's your place about again?
Encouraging kids
in their love of music. Axel.
Ah.
Like I said. room for both of us.
You know. just to be clear.
he did not leave the band.
We kicked him out.
I know. I know. It's okay.
Question: What do you say
you and I break away later
and I finally take you on a first date?
Answer: I'd like that.
Check. check. One. two. Check. check.
One. two. Check. check. check.
Wow.
I know. right? That's all I've been saying
since I got off the boat.
Come on.
- Ready?
- We really shouldn't be here.
It's so obvious this guy's just doing this
to get back at Brown.
First. he tries to take down
the White Crows. and now Camp Rock.
What is that?
Hot chocolate. They're handing it out free
when you walk in.
plus you get to keep the mug.
What?
There's no way I'm staying
at this bonfire.
Hey. pouty boy. You better hurry.
The bonfire's about to start.
You know. we should probably
go take our seats.
- I think they're about to start.
- Mm-hm.
- Don't mock.
- I'm not.
- Yes. you are.
- Okay. just a little bit.
Look. they actually have a real Wardrobe
Department with incredible fabric.
And they let me make this.
Uh-oh. I think I just sewed
my scarf to my bra.
So I thought this was supposed
to be a campfire.
You know. singing. telling stories.
an actual fire.
Everybody have a seat.
I'm Axel Turner.
And I'd like to welcome all you rockers.
and my dear. old friend. Brown Cesario...
Yeah. Brown! Whoo!
to Camp Star!
Go. Brown!
But you all don't wanna hear a speech
from me.
You wanna get to what a campfire
is really all about:
Singing.
Hey. that's what you just said.
You're twins.
So does anyone have anything
they'd like to play?
Camp Rockers. don't be shy.
Well. we'll go. if nobody else wants to.
This song is about me
and a friend of mine.
We're like a melody with no words
Until we figure it out
We sing. "la. la. la. la. la. la"
I know it's simple. yeah
But it's worked right up till now
'Cause up till now. yeah
Every day's been like a dream world
Oh. but now you're not just in my head
Oh. no
Will we remember different summers?
It's like tossing your heart
To see where it lands
Heads is easy
Tails is harder to plan
If we're starting all over again
And again and again
Oh. you know that I can't help but wonder
What's gonna happen next
I'm a little curious
Oh. yeah
Every star that I stood under
When you were under it too
Did you ever think about us?
I hope you did
'Cause I can tell you
That's something I'll never forget
I won't forget
If we remember different summers
It's like tossing your heart
To see where it lands
Heads is easy
Tails is harder to plan
If we're starting all over again
Only friends
Just beginning
But I hope that we find it again
So we can go from here
Oh
Will we remember different summers?
It's like tossing your heart
To see where it lands
Heads is easy
Tails is harder to plan
If we're starting all over again
Oh-oh
Again and again and again and again
Again and again and again
Will we remember different summers?
Whoo!
That was sweet.
But I guess it's time for Camp Star
to answer.
And. heh. my apologies
if we embarrass ourselves.
We're kind of new at this.
Nobody's gonna wanna get next to me
- 'Cause they know
- They know
I take what's mine and won't let it go
Doesn't matter
How you approach the scene
- Just hope
You're everything and more
When you hit the door
I dare you to challenge me
You'll be beggin' for mercy. please
Just watch
I'll give you something to follow
'Cause I've been waitin' so patiently
- To let the
- Fire come out in me
I'm what you're up against
Just letting you know
I keep giving you the fire
I'm gonna heat it up under my control
Here's the night
That you've been waitin' on
Fire
I'm gonna light it up
Gotta make it hot
The stage is mine
I'll set it on
The king is gone
And no one can take his crown
- So brave
They can't cool me off
When I hit the stage
Burning hot
The spotlight just spelled my name
- I feel famous
- Famous
The crowd cheers me on
They can't get enough
I dare you to challenge me
You'll be beggin' for mercy. please
Just watch
I'll give you something to follow
'Cause I've been waitin' so patiently
Fire come out in me
I'm what you're up against
Just letting you know
I keep giving you the fire
I'm gonna heat it up under my control
Here's the night
That you've been waitin' on
Fire
I'm gonna light it up. gotta make it hot
The stage is mine
I'll set it on
I keep giving you the fire
I'm gonna heat it up under my control
Here's the night
That you've been waitin' on
Fire
I'm gonna light it up. gotta make it hot
The stage is mine
I'll set it on
Fire
- Ow!
- Nate. are you okay?
You guys rock!
And that's how we do things
here at Camp Star!
- Wow.
- Ha-ha-ha!
Before we go any further.
I'd like to make a quick announcement.
We're having staffing problems.
Who knew we'd be so popular?
All right. now we're under attack.
So I'd just like to put it out there.
If there are any Camp Rock
counselors or staff
who'd like to make the switch.
I'd be more than willing
to double your salary.
You've gotta be joking.
I barely have enough staff as it is.
- I'll go.
- What?
- Count me in.
- No.
And if there are any Camp Rock campers
who'd like to join us.
well. I'm sure we can find you a bunk.
Oh. did I mention
our cabins are air-conditioned?
He can't do this.
Right. I need all the Camp Rockers
back on the boats now. Come on.
- Go. please.
- Come on. guys. Back to the boats.
Let's go. Come on.
Are you sure it's okay?
Not a scratch.
- I'm really sorry about that.
- Oh. it's all good. I'm totally fine.
I'm just happy I could catch it for you.
Well. it's always
kind of been my lucky charm.
I guess it still works.
Did you forget the part
where you hit him in the eye?
I'll be over there.
So. Dana. you were amazing up there.
You think?
I'm just glad it's finally over.
We've been practicing for weeks.
and still. every time I go on.
I'm almost sure I'm gonna throw up.
I'm really glad you guys came.
My dad was totally sure
none of you would show.
My dad's Axel Turner.
He's your dad?
Everybody says that.
and kind of exactly like that.
but trust me. once you get to know him.
he's a really great guy.
Well. I guess I should go.
Here. You don't wanna lose it.
You can keep it if you want.
- What would I do with a bracelet?
- Right.
For the record. I'm glad you're okay.
You have really pretty eyes.
Sorry. that was weird. I didn't mean
to make you uncomfortable.
No. it's all good.
People tell me that all the time.
Probably because
they're right in the middle of my face. so...
So...
What...?
- Um. I'll see you around.
- Okay.
Yes. I wanna keep it.
you have pretty eyes too. Stupid.
- I'm an idiot.
- Wow.
Something we both can agree on.
Ow! Strong idiot.
I... I don't want you talking to that boy.
Don't worry.
I don't think it's gonna be a problem.
Okay. come on.
Rockers. boats now.
Wow. Now. this is a recording studio.
Hey.
Um. hi.
Can I help you with something?
Do I look like I need help?
- Do I know you?
- That's funny. I'm Luke.
Luke Williams.
I was just on-stage.
like two minutes ago.
I'm giving you the fire
- Wow. impressive.
- I know. right? It's kind of my thing.
So you thinking about joining us
over here?
No. I'm perfectly happy where I am.
Well. you are Shane Gray's girlfriend.
so...
Wait. what does Shane...?
How do you even know that?
You have to know the players
if you wanna be in the game. right?
- No.
- It's a tough business.
It's summer camp.
To you. but to anybody at Camp Star.
it's step one to a long
and illustrious career.
I don't have time for second-rate.
- We're not second-rate.
- You don't have to get all defensive.
It's none of my business.
you don't have to try to convince me.
I'm not trying to do anything.
Good.
You're at the perfect place for you.
Look. just so we're clear.
Luke "I'm giving you the fire" Williams.
or whatever your name is.
not one Camp Rocker.
not in a million years.
would ever even think about coming over
to this narcissistic. over-produced
ego factory.
Guess what. My mom said yes.
I get to make the switch.
That's great.
Welcome to the ego factory.
Thanks.
Tess. how could you?
Oh. I'm so sorry. I feel horrible. but...
Who am I kidding? I am so excited.
I can't even pretend to be sympathetic.
That was great what you did up there.
I'm giving you the fire
- So impressive.
- I know. right?
Wow.
Good luck trying to find a spotlight
big enough for the both of you.
No. you guys. it's gonna be okay.
I mean. Brown's a smart guy.
he can figure something out.
Thanks for that vote of confidence.
Mitchie.
Guess I don't have to get
everyone's attention.
So the good news is.
and this really warms my heart.
we lost very few campers last night.
That's right.
But we did lose
quite a few of our remaining staff.
Which means.
and I can't believe I have to say this.
Camp Rock is closed.
effective immediately.
- Wait. what?
- No.
You have to believe me. I truly...
I've got no other option.
I'll start calling parents
as soon as we're done here.
which I guess is now.
I'm sorry.
Brown. wait. Guys.
Camp is over? But we just got here.
It's not his fault. I mean.
there's nothing he can do about it.
Man. this is such a bummer.
But...
...that doesn't mean
there isn't something we can do about it.
- What?
- Mitchie.
No. I'm serious.
This is our summer.
and we're not giving up.
- We're not backing down.
- Right.
I don't know. Mitchie.
We can't. we can't back down
Not right now. we can't back down
We can't back down
Ooh. ooh. yeah. yeah
Don't close your eyes
We're all in this together
Wherever they draw the line
We're not gonna straddle. we'll cross it
Or lose it
We can't back down
There's too much at stake
This is serious. don't walk away
We can't pretend it's not happening
In our own backyard
Our own home plate
- We've been called out
- Do you hear your name?
- Yeah
I'm not confused
Let's win this thing
We can't back down
There's too much at stake
Don't walk away
- Don't walk away
Yeah. yeah. yeah
Don't get me wrong
I don't like confrontation
I'd rather we all just get along
Music should be undivided
United
We can't back down
There's too much at stake
This is serious
Don't walk away
We can't pretend it's not happening
In our own backyard
Our own home plate
- We've been called out
- Do you hear your name?
- Yeah
I'm not confused. let's win this thing
We can't back down
There's too much at stake
Don't walk away
Yeah. yeah. yeah. yeah
We've got a situation
That we can't ignore
'Cause ignorance is not bliss
We don't have to take this. no
With every big decision
Comes an equally important
Share of the risk
- We've gotta take this. ohh
- We can't back down
- There's too much at stake
- Too much
This is serious
Don't walk away
We can't pretend it's not happening
In our own backyard
Our own home plate
We've been called out
- Do you hear your name?
- We've been called out
I'm not confused. let's win this thing
- We can't back down
- We've been called out
- There's too much at stake
Don't walk away. don't walk away
We can't back down
Not right now
What's going on?
Well. you said you needed
some new counselors.
so I found you some.
Then it looks like
I should call this staff meeting to order.
- Yes!
- Thank you.
- Yes.
- All right.
Come on. Terry.
No. nada. Guys. I already told you.
I'm not gonna be doing this.
Jason. you're looking at this all wrong.
This isn't punishment. It's a reward.
- Really?
- Really.
This just means that everybody thinks
that you have the leadership skills.
the maturity. the intelligence...
- You think I'm intelligent?
- No.
- and the sheer guts
to take on this challenge.
- Wow. you're good.
- Thank you.
You're right. This is an honor.
Exactly.
Now. get in there and make us proud.
We'll be right here if you need us.
All right.
- Run.
Hi. everybody. I'm Jason.
I'm gonna be your counselor.
I'm a little new at this so I thought
you guys would go a little bit easier on me.
What do you say?
I say. let's get him.
- Yeah!
- Guys. guys. hold on a minute.
Now get him.
No. no. no.
All right. let's dance.
Sorry.
- All good?
- All good.
Let's do this.
Yes. Yes. yes. yes.
Here we go. guys. All right.
Circle. down. Head. meet. out.
- Louder.
- La. la. la. la. la. la
Awesome.
We got a color that looks good with his
eye color. What about this. girls? Right?
Hi.
Enough.
Do you wanna rock?
Well. you know what?
You don't deserve to rock.
Why should I show you
the first thing about being a rock star.
if you don't wanna show me
any respect?
Well. okay. then.
Who wants to play the drums?
Who wants to play the guitar?
Who wants to be a lead singer?
Well. you are gonna have to buy tighter
pants and learn how to play a tambourine.
- I heard that.
- Sorry.
It's true.
- Nate?
- Yeah.
Shane. Heh. What's up. bro?
What are you doing?
Um. lifeguard duty.
Schedule's a mess.
but you can't be too careful.
Just one last look.
All clear.
So. what do I have to do
to pull you away from this clipboard?
Mitchie. I just rolled 100 pounds
of raw hamburger all by myself.
I told you. honey. I needed help.
No. no. no. that's impossible.
I know for a fact that I scheduled...
- Absolutely nobody. I'm so sorry.
- What's going on?
This isn't working.
The kitchen is a disaster.
Yesterday.
I ordered 50 pounds of black beans
and they delivered
50 cases of beach balls instead.
Well. you gotta admit. Mom.
you don't have the best handwriting.
Whoa. whoa. whoa.
Okay. it's rock 'n' roll. right?
It's gonna be a little chaotic.
I think you're doing great. We'll just make
some adjustments to the schedule. yeah?
Perfect.
Shane. help Connie with the hamburgers.
Actually. I've... I've got this thing...
- Oh. really? Well. come on. pretty boy.
- No. but...
All right. that's it. Now pick it up.
Bring it home.
I knew you could do it.
All right. now it's getting a little late.
so. what do you say
we all go enjoy some free time?
- Yeah.
- All right.
Hey. man. What are you doing?
Why does everybody keep doing that?
Sorry. we're just doing our part
as activity directors.
And what's the activity today?
Wakeboarding.
No!
Are you okay?
Yeah. I'm great.
Don't suppose you came over here
to see anyone in particular.
No. just getting some exercise.
Do you play a lot of sports?
Canoeing. That's pretty much it.
I'm really not all that sporty either. I played
soccer when I was little. but who doesn't?
I don't know if it counts as a sport.
but I'd kind of love to be a dancer.
It's like my nerdy secret. "if I could
be anything. that's what I'd be" wish.
What would you be?
I don't know. Never thought about it.
Probably because if you could
be anything. you'd be you.
Uh. do you wanna hear something
really stupid?
I was goofing around and I accidentally
sort of wrote your name on my hand
but used permanent ink by mistake.
No one's ever written my name
on their hand before.
Really more my wrist.
- Dana...
- Yeah?
Dana?
Oh. it's my dad. I'm so sorry.
I'm not supposed to be talking to you.
Hurry. Go.
Dana?
- Dana.
- Hey.
- I saw this canoe.
- Ugh.
Don't touch it. it's one of theirs.
I'll have an attendant fish it out.
- What's that on your wrist?
- Nothing.
You wanna know what I wanna be?
The kind of guy
who can tell you how he really feels.
I hate canoes.
- I'm still an idiot.
- I still agree.
Dude. you can't keep hitting me.
Thank you.
Ow!
Thanks. Mitchie.
I had absolutely the best day ever.
- Everything's finally starting to work out.
- That's great. It's all because of you.
No. it's because of us.
Now that everybody else
has gotten your time.
I think I'm gonna demand
some of my own.
It hasn't been that bad.
The whole reason I'm here.
the reason my brothers are here.
is so I can get to know you better.
It's only been like two seconds.
And that is the sweetest thing
that anybody has ever said to me.
- But...
And now a word
from your friendly neighborhood announcer.
Will the counselors scheduled for
the bonfire please report to the mess hall?
- But you gotta go.
- But we gotta go.
Are you coming?
No. it's cool. I'll catch up.
- Shane.
- Go. they need you.
Okay.
- Hey. I'm impressed.
- Eh.
You seem to be doing
much better with them.
It took a little bit of time.
but I think I finally gained their respect.
Who glued me to this log?
Log Butt. log Butt!
We're gonna call you Log Butt!
You know what's worse
than being called Log Butt?
Is being sat on by Log Butt.
Oh! Whoo!
Run. Run. he's got you.
Come back here.
Fireflies.
- I'm gonna get this one.
- Okay. catch them. everybody.
Let's jump. Jump.
Looks like the Lord of the Flies
over there.
There's no way they're gonna make it
through the summer.
I remember doing that. It's fun.
Don't even think about it.
It felt so great just standing up
in front of that class today.
I feel like there's nothing we can't do.
Pleats. Still can't do pleats.
Wish we had that attitude
the other night at Camp Star.
Yeah. I so wanted to show them up.
That hardly counted.
They'd been planning that for weeks.
Yeah. and now they're all walking around
thinking they're better than us.
So not true.
You know. I'd really like to see them
go up against us.
Yeah.
If we had time to get it together.
there's no way they'd stand a chance.
Like in Final Jam.
There's just no way.
Lot of big talk. Wanna see if it's true?
It's about time. My private vocal lessons
started ten minutes ago.
Oh. I'm sorry.
I forgot that Axel thinks
you need the extra rehearsal.
Camp Rock!
Camp Rock! Huh!
Yeah. that's right.
We're here on your stage.
See. you guys didn't really give us
a chance to answer back the other night.
But guess what. That's gonna change.
Camp Rock vs. Camp Star. the Final Jam.
What do you guys think about that?
Drums.
A little guitar. please.
One. two. three. four
I hope you're ready
For the time of your life
Just look at me
I put a gleam in your eye
Buckle up
We're gonna take you for a ride
Let's go
We got you goin' good in the vibe
- Everybody. put your hands to the sky
- Hands to the sky
Buckle up
We're gonna take you. take you high
Ooh. ooh
Show me. show me. show me. show me
Show what you got
Come on. come on. come on. come on
Ready or not
La. la. la. la. la. la
Let me see how you bop
It's on. it's on. it's on
Get crazy. crazy. crazy
Take it over the top
'Cause. because
Because when we rock
We let it rock
Rock it. rock it. rock it. rock it
Dance till we drop
It's on. it's on. it's on
- Whoo
- Okay. now
- Are you ready?
- Yeah
One. two
One. two. three. four
Show stoppin'
When I step in the place
Before it's done
You're gonna beg me to stay
Get onboard
Come on. let's ride the wave
- Okay
- Let's go. let's go. we just do what we do
Watch me break and pop
I'll pass it to you
You wanna rock like us
'Cause we're never second place
You ready. ready?
Show me. show me. show me
Show me. show what you got
Come on. come on. come on. come on
Ready or not
La. la. la. la. la. la
Let me see how you bop
It's on. it's on. it's on
Get crazy. crazy. crazy
Take it over the top
'Cause. because
Because when we rock
We let it rock
Rock it. rock it. rock it. rock it
Dance till we drop
It's on. it's on. it's on
Okay. now
Are you ready?
One. two. one. two. three
There. there. there. there
There is no competition
That's why
We in the number-one position
That crew can't hang with us
Man. we're too dangerous
Ain't got the style or the stamina
Just doin' my thing
Get hooked on my swing
Rockin' the place. droppin' the bass
Making all the girls sing
Yeah. we make the bells ring
- It's on. it's on
- Drums
Yeah
- Come on.
- Yeah.
A little guitar. please.
One. two. three. four.
Yeah.
Show me. show me. show me. show me
Show what you got
Come on. come on. come on
Come on. ready or not
La. la. la. la. la. la
Let me see how you bop
- It's on. it's on. it's on
- Show me
Get crazy. crazy. crazy
Take it over the top
'Cause. because
Because when we rock
We let it rock
Rock it. rock it. rock it. rock it
Dance till we drop
It's on. it's on. it's on
Show me. show me. show me
Show me. show what you got
Come on. come on. come on. come on
Ready or not
La. la. la. la. la. la
Let me see how you bop
It's on. it's on. it's on
Get crazy. crazy. crazy
Take it over the top
'Cause. because
Because when we rock
We let it rock
Rock it. rock it. rock it. rock it
Dance till we drop
It's on. it's on. it's on
- It's on
- It's on. it's on
- Two. one. two. three
It's on
That is a fantastic idea.
Truly. I'm impressed.
A little healthy competition
is exactly what we need.
A champion always needs
a good sparring partner.
We do?
But you really think that
you can take my guys on head-to-head?
- Any time. any place.
- Yup.
- Yeah.
- Can't wait.
Maybe use our amphitheatre.
Doesn't matter where.
We just know that Camp Rock is gonna
blow you guys away.
- That's right.
- Straight up.
I'm sure an audience
would be a better judge of that.
Bring it on.
You can pack it with anybody you want.
Well. how about a worldwide audience?
What if we put this little competition
on TV?
Have the public decide
who's really the best.
TV? We'd really get to be on TV?
Uh. I don't really know about this.
Not such a big talker now. are you?
Ooh.
- But that would be so cool.
- The whole world would see us.
Uh...
Come on. Mitchie. This could be huge.
Yeah. let's do it.
You're on.
- All right.
- Yeah.
I wrote this song a long time ago
and I kind of forgot about it.
but I think it could work.
It's a duet.
Now. But I think I could rewrite it
and make a part for everybody.
Or we can rewrite it.
"I lay pretty. pretty flowers
on your grave."
Am I the only one who thinks this song is.
like. totally depressing?
Ahem. You're on the wrong page.
Yeah. that song
was for my hamster's funeral.
Oh. this is perfect.
The staging could be pretty cool.
Yeah. it looks like there's some
great spots for dancing.
And it's got a great groove.
Well. before we get ahead of ourselves.
guys. I got a couple conditions.
You've got conditions?
Yes. Well. a condition.
There has to be a spot
for my junior rockers.
Of course. That's what this is all about.
So. what do you guys think?
- I'm in.
- Let's do it.
I think somebody should talk
to Uncle Brown.
Why? I already know
what he's gonna say.
How could she do that? I told them.
I told Mitchie
Axel Turner cannot be trusted.
I don't know why
you're getting so upset.
At the very least. Camp Rock
could get some great exposure.
He took advantage. is what he did.
He saw an opportunity and went for it.
An opportunity to destroy me
once and for all.
And I thought Mitchie
could be dramatic.
Okay. then. just call him and say no.
It's not that big a deal.
Oh. we're well past big deal.
Look. "Camp Wars." Catchy.
Yeah. I especially like the tagline.
"Only one will survive."
Millions of viewers will be watching.
That's good. right?
After this. we are done.
And not just for the summer. for good.
Oh. come on. Brown.
Give them a chance.
Look. nobody believes in
my rockers more than I do.
but we are gonna look like a joke
next to Camp Star.
We don't have the resources.
the infrastructure. the money.
Talent. passion. commitment.
yeah. we've got that.
It's not gonna matter.
It always matters.
And when people watch.
where do you think
they're gonna send their kids to camp?
- She didn't do it on purpose.
- I know.
I just wish she wouldn't have
fallen into the trap.
Good morning. Camp Rock.
A message from Mitchie Torres:
All rockers. please report
to the main stage immediately.
Yeah. that means you. Get moving.
All right. rockers. There are
new schedules out on the board.
From this moment on. everything
is about winning the competition.
Everything.
We have to be completely focused.
What about swimming
and waterskiing and...?
Focus. Sorry.
Oh. Sorry again.
Seriously. you guys.
if we wanna save this camp.
we have to put
all of our energies into this
and make it the best performance
that any of us have ever put on.
I mean. we may have our doubters.
but we have come way too far
just to back down. Agreed?
Agreed.
All right. Now. let's go get to work.
Now.
I don't know what to do about this set.
but it's just gotta be big.
Think of the biggest thing you can imagine
and then make it bigger.
- All right.
- Thanks.
Mitchie. we're moving
in the wrong direction.
There's even less time on this
than the last one.
- I've got a few minutes now.
- That's not what I mean.
Mitchie. can you look at this?
I want us to coordinate.
but not be all matchy-matchy.
- Mitchie... Hi. Shane.
- Hi.
I know you're rewriting. but we've gotta
make some decisions about the music.
Mitchie. can I talk to you?
Do you know who's doing
the vocal arrangements?
If it's me. fine.
but somebody's gotta tell me.
I'm sorry.
I don't even know why I'm here.
Take my advice
and never get a girlfriend.
I don't think that'll be a problem.
Hey. what are you guys doing?
I thought you were gonna be rehearsing.
Whoa. calm down.
We've been rehearsing for over five hours.
We're just taking a little break.
Really? Because I was watching.
and it looks like we're gonna need
a lot more work.
- You guys done already?
- No.
He was just telling me this story
about his sister. It's hilarious. Tell her.
The one about the group of kids
that didn't take their jobs seriously
and then the camp shut down?
Yeah. I think I've heard it.
Hey. Mitchie. You gotta check out this bit
me and the J.R.'s worked out.
It's a real spotlight moment.
That's great. I'm sure whatever it is.
it's just gonna have to be
more of a background moment.
Sander. what's going on?
You guys haven't made any progress
since I left like half an hour ago.
You guys have to get this thing built.
You guys have to work with me.
If I wanted to go to Camp Star
I would have signed up.
Okay. that's not fair.
I'm just trying to get stuff done.
but if you guys don't care...
Mitchie.
We all care. but you gotta lighten up.
Really? And what will that get us?
All right. okay. Let's do it again.
That girl is taking the F-U-N
out of summer.
There is no F-U-N in "summer."
- Exactly.
- Seriously.
I love her. but I'm gonna kill her.
Okay. I think you know
what you've gotta do.
I'm on it.
Guys. guys. calm down.
She didn't say no.
she said she'd think about it.
All work and no spray
makes a very unhappy rocker.
So I got a proposition for you guys.
You think you're up for it?
Okay. we have a ton of stuff to go over.
Where is everybody?
Seriously. people have got to start
being on time.
Attack!
Oh. this was not on the schedule.
Are you kidding?
This is what summer camp is all about.
Counterattack!
Oh. ho!
Come on! Ha. ha!
Come on. then.
- I know.
- It's so high.
- Look at that.
- That's a lot of fire there.
- So fun today.
- Today was so awesome.
- Yeah.
- Has anybody seen Mitchie?
Um. I don't know. She missed dinner.
Okay. thanks.
Look at our fire.
Your sheet music's soggy.
Just pouring myself into my music.
- That was bad.
- Yeah. I know. Um...
- Are you here to help?
- I can't.
Why?
Because you and I are going
on a moonlight picnic.
- Now?
- Right now.
- How could you...
- Because I'm that nice of a guy.
think that I would just go running off?
Are you saying no?
Do you not understand
everything that needs to get done?
How could I not?
You remind me every two seconds.
And the water-balloon fight.
I mean. what were you thinking?
I was thinking.
"Wouldn't it be nice to have a little fun?"
So you're saying I'm not fun?
Why do I even keep trying?
The whole reason I came was because...
I know. It was to get to know me better.
Well. guess what. This is me
trying to save something that I care about.
- So am I.
- Really? How's that working out for you?
Not so great.
Shane.
You forgot your flashlight.
It's like he doesn't hear a word I say
His mind is somewhere far away
And I don't know how to get there
- It's like all he wants is to chill out
- She's way too serious
- He makes me wanna pull all my hair out
- She's always in a rush and interrupting
- Like he doesn't even care
- Like she doesn't even care
- You
- Me
We're face to face
- But we don't see eye to eye
- Like fire and rain
- You can drive me insane
- But I can't stay mad at you for anything
- We're Venus and Mars
- We're like different stars
- Like different stars
But you're the harmony
To every song I sing
- And I wouldn't change a thing
She's always tryin' to save the day
Just wanna let my music play
She's all or nothing
But my feelings never change
- Why does he try to read my mind?
- I try to read her mind
- It's not good to psychoanalyze
- She tries to pick a fight to get attention
- It's what all of my friends say
- You
- Me
We're face to face
But we don't see eye to eye
- Like fire and rain
- You can drive me insane
- But I can't stay mad at you for anything
- We're Venus and Mars
- We're like different stars
- Like different stars
You're the harmony
To every song I sing
- And I wouldn't change a thing
When I'm yes. she's no
When I hold on he just lets go
- We're perfectly imperfect
- But I wouldn't change a thing. no
- We're like fire and rain
- Like fire and rain
- You can drive me insane
- But I can't stay mad at you for anything
- We're Venus and Mars
- We're like different stars
- Like different stars
But you're the harmony
To every song I sing
- And I wouldn't change a thing
- But I can't stay mad at you for anything
- We're Venus and Mars
- We're like different stars
- Like different stars
But you're the harmony
To every song I sing
- And I wouldn't change a
- Wouldn't change a thing
Where is everybody?
All right. now let's all look
at the alto harmony on measure 15.
There's a four-bar rest.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
- Oh. hold on.
- What's going on?
You were right.
It shouldn't be all up to you.
And we do need to step it up.
Shane got everybody up before dawn.
He can be pretty persuasive
when he wants to be.
Morning. Sleep well?
I don't think you got
the new arrangement yet.
Needed a lot of work.
You did this?
- We all did.
- Yeah.
I already know I'm gonna love it.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
All right. let's get started.
We gotta rock this stage
like we own it. right?
Now. I can hear you.
but I gotta see you play.
- Nate. show them how it's done.
- Like this.
Excellent.
Jason. show them how to rock.
Okay. guys. not like this:
But like this:
Good job.
Well. it's easy for you guys.
but we're not all rock stars.
But you can be.
Oh
Yeah
All right
Mm-hm-hm
Gather round. guys
It's time to start listenin'
Practice makes perfect
But perfect's not workin'
There's a lot more to music
Than knowing where your cue's gonna be
You can play all the right notes
But that don't mean you're moving me
But if you can jump like David Lee Roth
Or pump your fist
Like you're Bruce the Boss
If you got heart and soul
You can rock 'n' roll
Rock 'n' roll
Strum it. drum it
Slide across and run it
The stage is your home
If you learn how to own it
Like the greats did
There's no way that you can fake it
You've gotta feel the beat
Before you can move
Even though you're not wearing
Blue suede shoes
And makin' mistakes
Well. that won't matter
If you can swagger
Like you're Mick Jagger
If you've got heart and soul
You can rock 'n' roll
Whoo. solo
If you live and die for the music inside
If the one-four-five never gets old
Then you can rock 'n' roll
Rock 'n' roll
All right. now. take it low
Now. I need the spotlight
To hit me right here
As the crowd starts to cheer
I need the fan to blow
Right through my rock-star hair
Right here
If you can scream like Axl Rose
Or sing like Christina show after show
If you've got heart and soul
- You can rock 'n' roll
- Yeah
If you've got heart and soul
You can rock 'n' roll
Ooh. yeah
Oh
Yeah
All right
- Hi. Nate.
- Whoa!
Oh! Oh. I'm so sorry. Are you okay?
Hi. Dana.
- What are you doing here?
- What do you think?
- You came to see me?
- Good guess.
Well. here I am.
Heh. That's it?
I came all the way over here in a canoe
risking my father's wrath.
and that's all you have to say to me?
I don't know what else
I'm supposed to say.
There's nothing you're supposed to say.
Every day I see you looking and waving
and I'm all.
"That's so sweet. I so like him."
You do? Really. that's what you say?
- But then...
- "But then"?
That's never good.
How do I really know
if I don't know anything about you?
- I guess I just thought you were different.
- I am different.
No. you're not.
You're exactly like
every other teenage boy in the world.
Have you ever told me anything
about yourself?
You know. other than you like canoeing.
Well. I don't really like canoeing.
Oh. Oh. good.
So I really know nothing about you.
I still don't know
what I'm supposed to say.
I think you just did.
Words don't come easy
Idiot.
Without a melody
I'm always thinkin'
In terms of do-re-mi
I should be hikin'. swimmin'
Laughin' with you
Instead I'm all out of tune
Special order.
But what you don't know
You lift me off of the ground
Your inspiration
You help me find my sound
Just like a bass line in half time
You hold down the groove
That's why I'm countin' on you
- And when I hear you on the radio
- I never want to change a single note
- It's what I tried to say all along
- You're my favorite song
My favorite song
- And when I hear you on the radio
- And when I hear you on the radio. yeah
- I never want to change a single note
No. no
It's what I tried to say all along
You're my favorite song
I take back what I said about girlfriends.
It's all good. because at this rate.
I'll never have one.
What do you mean?
- Well. there's this girl.
- I kind of figured.
I really like her. but I'm having a hard time
telling her how I really feel.
You're a rock star. dude. Use it.
I don't think she cares.
She just wants to know all this stupid.
random stuff about me.
It's not random stuff.
She just wants to know you care enough
to let her know who you are.
Well. I care.
But I just don't know how to say it.
Well. if you can't say it. you can sing it.
Every single time
I'm trying to sing my high note.
I keep getting lost behind her big head.
- Oh. no. you didn't.
- You couldn't stand the spotlight.
Now that you mention.
I'm not trying to do anything.
Enough.
We'll run it again in three minutes.
And this time. remember.
it's not amateur hour.
He means you.
- Hi. Dana.
- Ah!
Kind of makes you jump. doesn't it?
- You shouldn't be here.
- I know. but I couldn't wait.
Wait for what?
It's a list of things
that nobody knows about me.
Two minutes.
I really gotta go. I'm sorry.
Wait. We still have two minutes.
Okay.
I'm. I'm good at wasting time
I think lyrics need to rhyme
And you're not askin'
But I'm tryin' to grow a mustache
I eat cheese
But only on pizza. please
And sometimes
On a homemade quesadilla
Otherwise it smells like feet to me
And I. I really like it
When the moon looks like a toenail
And I love it when you say my name
Places. everybody. Come on.
If you wanna know. here it goes
Gonna tell you there's a part of me
That shows if we're close
Gonna let you see everything
But remember that you asked for it
I'll try to do my best to impress
But it's easier to let you take a guess
At the rest
But you wanna hear
What lives in my brain and my heart
Well. you asked for it
For your perusing. at times confusing
Slightly amusing
Introducing me
Do-do. do-do. do-do-do
La-da. da-da
La-da. da-da. da-da
Da-da. da
Come on.
get a move on. We don't have all day.
I never trust a dog to watch my food
And I like to use the word "dude"
As a noun or an adverb or an adjective
And I. I never really been into cars
I like really cool guitars
And superheroes
And checks with lots of zeros on 'em
I love the sound of violins
And makin' someone smile
If you wanna know. here it goes
Gonna tell you there's a part of me
To show if we're close
Gonna let you see everything
But remember that you asked for it
I'll try to do my best to impress
But it's easier to let you take a guess
At the rest
But you wanna hear
What lives in my brain and my heart
Well. you asked for it
For your perusing. at times confusing
Possibly amusing
Introducing me
Well. you probably know
More than you ever wanted to
So be careful when you ask next time
Dana.
So if you wanna know. here it goes
Gonna tell you
There's a part of me to show if we're close
Gonna let you see everything
But remember that you asked for it
I'll try to do my best to impress
But it's easier to let you take a guess
At the rest
But you wanna hear
What lives in my brain and my heart
Well. you asked for it
For your perusing. at times confusing
Hopefully amusing
Introducing me
Do-do. do-do. do-do-do
Do-do. do-do
Introducing me
Dana. Everyone's waiting.
Sorry. It's my fault.
Why don't you save the theatrics
for the competition?
It's okay. Go.
Thank you.
We'll talk about this later.
And all that was left
was a bloody footprint.
- Lame.
- Not even scary.
Yeah. totally not scary at all.
Okay. time for bed. Turn on the lights.
- But you called "lights out."
- I know what I called.
What was that?
- Jason. do you think we're gonna win?
- Yeah. Jason.
Yeah. do you think we're gonna win?
Of course we're gonna win.
You guys are rock stars.
But what if they are too?
I guess I really didn't think about that.
Good night.
Everybody up.
Shh.
Follow my lead.
We're on a mission.
Okay. guys. stay low. Roll.
Oh. a rock. Ow. ow. ow! Oh!
Okay. Don't roll.
Okay. gently. guys. Come on. carefully.
Single file. Slow. Careful.
Come on. Shh.
Guys. come on.
Go. go.
You can play a song
Almost any groove
We can break it down
Break it down
Hey
You can play a song
When you see me move
Make you turn around
Turn around
Oh-ooh-oh
I know you
Are checkin' on me
I should be checkin' on you
Oh
Give me the green light
I'm ready to go
Here at the start line
I'm breaking the rope
- I'm gonna take you
- I'm gonna shake you
- No one's gonna lose
- Walkin' in my shoes
Won't stop at the red light
I'm on a roll
Turn up the music
I'm out of control
- I'm gonna take you
- I'm gonna shake you
- No one's gonna lose
- Walkin' in my shoes
When the lights come on
You can feel the heat
Then I'll hit the floor. hit the floor
Ooh
When the curtain's up
I fly on my feet
You'll be wantin' more
Wantin' more. ohhh
Oh-ooh-oh
I know you
Are checkin' on me
I should be checkin' on you
Oh
Give me the green light
I'm ready to go
Here at the start line
I'm breaking the rope
- I'm gonna take you
- I'm gonna shake you
- No one's gonna lose
- Walkin' in my shoes
Won't stop at the red light
I'm on a roll
Turn up the music
I'm out of control
- I'm gonna take you
- I'm gonna shake you
- No one's gonna lose
- Walkin' in my shoes
- Yeah
Walkin' in my shoes
- Give me the green light
- I'm ready to go
No one's gonna lose
Walkin' in my shoes
Give me the green light
I'm ready to go
Here at the start line
I'm breaking the rope
- I'm gonna take you
- I'm gonna shake you
- No one's gonna lose
- Walkin' in my shoes
Won't stop at the red light
I'm on a roll
Turn up the music
I'm out of control
- I'm gonna take you
- I'm gonna shake you
- No one's gonna lose
- Walkin' in my shoes
Go. go. go.
Walkin' in my shoes
Hey
- Well?
- Good.
Maybe great.
But this competition isn't about maybe.
Okay. fine.
But can you tell her to stay out of my light?
Well. maybe if you would stay
out of my way. it wouldn't be a problem.
Let me see "Tear it Down" instead.
Let's reset. people. Come on. Move!
This has to be perfect.
Camp Rock isn't gonna know
what hit them.
- And the stage was. like. super-cool.
- It's huge.
Wait. wait. wait. Hold up.
Wait. so it's just Tess and Luke singing?
Yeah. pretty much. Everybody else is doing
something. but they're definitely the stars.
But this makes it so much easier.
We could totally win this thing.
- How so?
- Oh. come on. Even I get it.
I don't care what they're singing.
but you and Shane are better
than Tess and Luke any day.
But Shane and I
aren't even singing together.
But you originally
wrote the song as a duet.
- I know. but I...
- You're our two strongest singers.
And we know you have chemistry.
It's just. everybody worked so hard.
Yeah. to help save the camp.
If the two of you singing alone on-stage
can help us win. you have to do it.
Then it's settled.
Remember when Audrey
jumped on Jason?
Man. the shaving cream
was the best one.
You guys okay
with just Shane and I singing?
Yeah. we're good. I was just looking
forward to doing some of my new moves.
But it's okay. if it means we get
to come back here next summer.
- You guys had a good summer?
- Only the best summer ever.
You guys just gave me
the best idea ever.
- Thank you.
- Ew! Gross!
Hey. guys. new plan.
Everyone meet in ten minutes.
Hello. and welcome to Hitz TV.
I'm Georgina Farlow.
And today we're bringing you Camp Wars.
the ultimate summer-camp showdown.
Now. there can be only one winner
this Final Jam.
and your votes
are gonna help us decide.
Just call or text in
after each performance...
Kids. make sure
to have your parents' permission.
- and let us know who you think sang out
and who you think hit a wrong note.
What's your favorite camp.
Camp Star or Camp Rock?
- And we're out.
- Okay.
Georgina.
- It's great to see you.
- As always. Axel.
Well. I'm gonna go backstage
and do some standups before the concert.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
All right. let's go get
some interviews backstage
with some of the campers.
- You. uh. know her?
- No. I know everyone.
But don't worry. she doesn't have
anything to do with the voting.
Oh.
So I probably shouldn't hold out hope
for us ever being friends again?
Probably not.
Though you never know. next year
I might hire you to run my summer camp.
Thanks.
But I'm already booked.
Good luck.
I'll be lucky if you don't
forget your words this time.
By "good luck" I mean
"I hope you fall off the stage."
As the sun goes down.
the volume goes up.
Welcome back to the ultimate
summer-camp showdown.
where you decide the winner.
Now. first up is Camp Star.
Now. Camp Star
was founded only this year
by superstar producer and founder
of Star Records. Axel Turner.
who's been producing
for over 20 years.
Now. I know if I was gonna study music.
this is the place I'd wanna be.
- Why is she saying that?
- It's her job.
She's supposed to say nice things.
If she doesn't stop talking.
I think I'm gonna throw up.
Too late.
Well. there's no turning back now.
because the party has already started.
Camp Star. everybody.
Tear it down
Yo. Luke.
I need you to do something for me.
I was ready for this
Since I was cradlin'
Put my name on the list
You won't be gamblin'
Not gonna leave with just this
We takin' everything
Confidence. compliments
I bet you see it's evident
Catch me if you can
I'm like a bandit
I can float on my feet
You can't stand it
I don't just dance in a group
I command it
We'll give you more than
You want and you can handle
When we're out on the floor
We'll take over the ball
Stealin' the show
We're gonna leave you in awe
When we're comin' up
We gonna tear it down
You can't stop us now
You can't shut us down
You can't top the sound
Better get ready now
We're gonna tear it down
The looks. we got 'em
The moves. we got 'em
The style. we got it
We gonna tear it down
The love. we got it
The crowd. we own it
Tonight. we run it
We gonna tear it down
Ooh
- We gonna tear it down
- Yes. yes. yes
Them no want to contest we
Recognize we the best that can be
Sing. dance and rap
Get hands to clap
Of course you know that
You can't hold a candle to our flames
Tear it up and we takin' names
It's not a game. it's a shame
You can't be like us
Can't be like us
We leave you in the dust
Of course we tear it up
When we're out on the floor
We'll take over the ball
Stealin' the show
We're gonna leave you in awe
When we're comin' up
We gonna tear it down
You can't stop us now
You can't shut us down
You can't top the sound
Better get ready now
We gonna tear it down
The looks. we got 'em
The moves. we got 'em
The style. we got it
We gonna tear it down
The love. we got it
The crowd. we own it
Tonight. we run it
We gonna tear it down
Camp Star. everyone.
Remember. if you loved them
as much as I did. call or text in now.
But don't go anywhere.
because in a moment
we're gonna hear from Camp Rock.
- What happened to you?
- When I get nervous I sparkle things.
- Would you stop and listen?
- You sounded good too.
- Hey. you guys were incredible.
- I know. right?
Only one thing would've made it better:
doing it solo.
I totally agree.
It's this bantery thing that we...
Thanks.
Good luck.
Quite a performance. eh?
No denying it.
But don't count
those votes just yet. love.
- I think you're gonna be very impressed.
- I don't need to be impressed.
- It'd be a miracle if Axel didn't win.
- Excuse me?
You know how much money
he spent marketing this?
He's paying to text and tweet every cell
phone user in the western hemisphere.
You don't even need to see the show
to know to vote for Camp Star.
One minute.
How come I just got a text
telling me to vote for Camp Star?
I just got one too.
It's asking me if I wanna download
Camp Star's song as my ringtone.
You were really a star.
Thanks.
And I really gotta go.
Oh. I hate crust on my bread.
and birds make me nervous.
Excuse me.
Oh. ah. that performance was amazing.
Thank you.
- Don't you have somewhere to be?
- Yes. but. you know.
once you start expressing your
innermost thoughts and feelings.
it's kind of hard to stop.
- Wish us luck.
- Good luck.
Dana. he is the enemy.
No. he's not. Not everything in life
is a competition.
But I think I just won.
And we're back. If you liked Camp Star.
get ready to be blown away
by Camp Rock.
Now. Camp Rock was founded
by rock icon
and legendary lead guitarist
Brown Cesario.
- You ready?
- Let's do this.
Ladies and gentlemen. Camp Rock.
They say that life is a two-way street
When you're not sure
You gotta trust your feet
To know the right way
You can keep on moving
With your head down
- Or you can stop and take a look around
- Take a look around
- And that's the choice I've made
- I've made. yeah
- It's for that movie inside your head
- Making memories we can't forget
And when you can't forget
You're gonna know
In your soul
This is what we came here for
- So live it loud
- Here and now
This moment. it won't be ignored
So why not open up that door?
It's what we came here for
- Oh. oh
- Oh. yeah
For every song we let play outside
The melodies we get to ride
- We get to ride
- Every time we sing
Oh. yeah. yeah. yeah
The friends we've made
The fun we've had
Remembering's gonna make me laugh
- It's a beautiful thing
- So beautiful
- I wanna send it around the world
All around the world
- 'Cause everybody should feel this good
'Cause when you feel this good
- You're gonna know
You're gonna know
In your soul
This is what we came here for
Oh. so live it loud
Here and now
This moment. it won't be ignored
You're gonna know
In your soul
This is what we came here for
- So live it loud
- Live it loud
Here and now
This moment. it won't be ignored
It won't be ignored
- So why not open up that door?
- Open up that door
So come on. open up that door
It's what we came here
Surprise!
- Oh. yeah
- Came here
For
It's what we came here
Came here for
Whoo!
Weren't they incredible?
So call in now. and tell us
which summer camp rules.
And don't go anywhere.
We'll be right back.
Call in. call in.
- Yes!
- Wow!
Impressive. but it'll never sell.
You know.
it should still be about the music.
Maybe so. but that's why
you'll never make it in this business.
That's fine.
I don't wanna be in your business.
And the results are in.
You know. I was thinking about
keeping this as a souvenir. Heh.
Can't believe we lost.
Every song can't be a hit.
Isn't that what you told me?
Doesn't mean we have to stop singing.
I'm really sorry I didn't spend
more time with you this summer.
- Hey. the whole reason I came here...
- Was to get to know me better.
And I've learned everything
I need to know.
So let's sing
Na. na-na-na. na
Hey. ya
Come on and sing
Na. na-na-na. na
Hey. ya
This is our song
That's all that matters
'Cause we all belong
Right here together
There's nothin' better
Than singin' along
This is our summer
This is our song
Come grab your guitar
Sit by the fire
'Cause we all need a song
When we're weary and tired
We'll sit here together
- And sing it out loud
This is our song
That's all that matters
'Cause we all belong
Right here together
There's nothin' better
Than singin' along
This is our summer
And this is our song
This is our song
What's that?
- Hi. we saw the fire.
- We really don't get to do this kind of thing.
So we were hoping there was room
for some of us to join.
There's always room.
If it's okay with you. I'd really like to
come back to Camp Rock next summer.
Come on.
Come on and sing
Na. na. na. na. na
Hey. ya
Hey. can I get a little help inside?
- The phones are going crazy.
- Yeah. sure. I'll help.
I told my parents I wanna come here
instead next summer.
Come on and sing
Na. na-na-na. na
Hey. ya
Please. can you put us on the list?
This place is so much more fun.
I'm sure we can work something out.
Come on and sing
Na. na-na-na. na
- Hey. ya
This is our song
That's all that matters
'Cause we all belong
Right here together
There's nothin' better
Than singin' along
- This is our summer
- Our summer
This is our song
That's all that matters
'Cause we all belong
Right here together
There's nothin' better
Than singin' along
This is our summer
And this is our song
- This is our song
We're all a go.
Camp Rock counselors. right?
- Let's do this.
- Let's do it.
- Camp Rock counselors.
- Yeah.
Marker.
All good?
Marker take three. Take five. Take nine.
- All good? Let's do this.
- All good.
Camp Rock counselors.
- I'm not laughing. Dead serious. y'all.
- Marker take 14.
She's the boss. she's serious.
We're all serious.
And action.
Marker take 16. Take 17. Take 18.
- Phew. Okay. we're good. All good?
- All good.
- Okay.
- Let's do this.
- What? All good?
- All good.
Stop it.
- I can feel you looking at me.
- Camp Rock counselors.